source-code dot text what this is gonna do is it's pretty much just going to
源代码点 文本 将会是什么 做的是它非常 简单， 只是去
take the text of this request all the crap that we need to crawl and we're
全部拿这个请求的文本 我们需要爬行的垃圾， 我们是
gonna store it in a variable called plain text so again we're not we don't really care about the extra crap that
将它存储在一个 名为 的变量中 纯文本 所以我们不是 不是 非常关心 额外的垃圾
happens behind the scenes we just want the text the links the images the good
发生在我们想要 的 幕后 文本链接图像的好处
meat of a website so right now all my good stuff is stored in plain text
一个网站的肉，所以现在 我 所有的 好东西以纯文本形式存储
that's what we can sift through so the only other kind of transition I need to
这就是我们可以通过这样的筛选 我只需要其他类型的过渡
make now is is pretty much this right now I have all the information from a
让现在是相当多这种 权利 现在我收到了来自的所有信息
webpage however since we're using this class right here beautifulsoup
然而 网页 ，因为我们正在使用这种 在这里上课beautifulsoup
we need to take that and convert it to a beautiful soup object and that's because
我们需要把它转换成一个 美丽的汤对象，那是因为
this class right here it needs its data formatted in a special way to be able to
这个类就在这里需要它的数据 以特殊的方式格式化能够
crawl through it and sit through and sort through like all the links to stuff
爬过它并坐下 来 像所有东西的链接一样排序
easily so my beautiful soup object I'm gonna store it you know object named
很容易，所以我的美丽汤对象我 要存储它你知道对象 命名
soup now in order to create an object it's actually really easy just put the
汤现在为了 创建一个对象 它实际上很简单
class name and the one parameter that you pass into it is that text so
类名和一个参数 你进入它是文本 ，以便
basically plain and simple this is all the source code from the website
基本上简单明了这就是全部 来自网站的源代码
whatever webpage we said to Crowe now when we have this soup object this soup
我们 现在 对克罗说的 任何 网页 当我们有这个汤反对此汤
object is the thing that we can sort through say okay find all the links in soup find all the titles in soup so I
对象是我们可以排序的东西 通过 说 好找到所有的链接 汤找到汤里的所有头衔所以我
know it's kind of confusing so far but you guys are going to see something
知道到目前为止它有点令人困惑但是 你们 会 看到什么
really cool right now so since we have all that data in soup we can do
真的很酷，所以我们有 我们可以做汤中的所有数据
something like this say we wanted to know what's an easy thing to do alright we'll say that we'll let's
像 这样说，我们想 知道什么是容易的事情 好吧，我们会说 ， 我们将让我们
gather just the the titles of each item so maybe we just wanted to make a web
只收集每个项目的标题 所以也许我们只想制作一个网站
crawler to gather the titles of each item just so we can sort through them
爬虫 收集 每个 的标题 项目只是为了我们可以对它们进行排序
easier well we just can't be like okay get the title of this how do we type it
更容易以及我们只是不能 像没事 得到这个标题我们如何键入它
in because even though that you know if we were talking to our friend then he
因为即使你知道如果 我们谈论我们的朋友 ，然后他
might see what the titles are Arkham Peter doesn't understand that language
可能会看到Arkham的头衔 彼得不懂那种语言
so what we need to do is if we right-click this inspect element we need
所以我们需要做的就是我们 右键单击 我们需要的 这个 inspect元素
to find something in this source code that is unique so we'll say okay
在这个源代码中找到一些东西 这是独特的所以我们会说 好的
this is the title right here so we can't just say links because you know my name
这是标题，所以我们不能 只是 说链接，因为你知道我的名字
is a link the categories are links what trait is
是一个链接 类别是链接的特征
specific to this title that we can tell beautifulsoup to use well actually this class right here item
具体到我们可以告诉的这个标题 beautifulsoup使用 实际上这个类就在这里
name no other links except the titles have that class so we can just copy that
除了标题之外没有其他链接 有那个班， 所以我们可以复制 它
and basically what we're going to say is okay gather all the links on this page
基本上我们 要说的是 好吧收集这个页面上的所有链接
but only if they have the class item name and whenever it does that it only
但只有他们有班级项目 名称，只要它只做它
gets the titles so in order to do that put for link in su find all now this parameter is gonna go through that
得到标题，以便这样做 把 用于链接苏 找到所有现在这 参数将经历这一点
source code and find all of a specific item depending on on the information to give it and I'll show you guys what I
源 代码并找到所有特定的 项目根据上的信息 给它，我会 告诉你们我是什么
mean right now so the first thing it says okay what element do you want me to
现在意味着第一件事 说好的，你想要我做什么
find well we want to find the links and of course links are named a for anchors
找好我们想 找到的链接， 当然链接被命名为锚点
in HTML so find all the links now if you just ran this it'll return all of the links go to return you know the category
在HTML中，如果你现在找到所有链接 只是跑了这个 它将返回所有的 链接去返回你知道的类别
names the ratings names we don't want that so we need to give it one more
命名我们不想要的评级名称 所以我们需要再给它一个
parameter and that's this add a comma and in between curly braces
参数和的 这款 添加一个逗号 在花括号之间
remember the item name was a class so it says okay you can either put the
记住项目名称是一个类，所以它 说没关系，你可以把它
attribute such as ID class arm so on and so forth there so it says okay what
属性如ID类 等等 所以那里说它没问题
attribute do you want me to look for and after this you add a colon and then you give it the value such as item name said
属性你想让我寻找和 在此之后你添加一个冒号，然后你 给它 项目名称 之类的值
that kind of item name a legume low so what this is going to do
那种项目名称豆类低 这是怎么回事
is it's gonna loop through all of your source code and it's gonna pick out the
它会循环通过你所有的 源代码，它会挑选出来的
links with a class of item name so again this is how we tell beautifulsoup to get
再次链接一类项目名称 这是我们如何告诉beautifulsoup 获得
all the titles I know it's kind of weird but hey it's a computer not so smart as
我知道的所有标题都有点奇怪 但是嘿，这是一台不那么聪明的电脑
us or maybe they're smarter than us no haven't really figured that out yet
我们或者他们 比 我们 聪明 还没有真正想到这一点
so right now it's plucking out all of the titles well okay I have like a
所以现在它拔除所有 的 标题还可以，我喜欢
million things to teach you well we were refreshes so I can so whenever we
亿个事教你怎么说我们 也 刷新，所以每当我们这样做时我都可以
inspect these elements this is what it's gathering basically whatever is highlighted right here but now saying
检查这些元素就是这样 什么是基本收集 在这里突出显示但现在说
okay well what do you want from here do you want the href pretty much your o do
好吧 ，你想从这里做什么呢 你想要href几乎是你的o
you want the class name do you want the crap that's inside here I mean this is a
你想要类名你想要吗？ 在这里的垃圾我的 意思是这是一个
lot of crap do you want me just to give it give everything to you back well
废话很多，你要我只 给 它给你一切回报
let's say that we actually only wanted the URL so the link address of each one so what we can do is we can say okay
让我们说我们实际上 只想要 URL所以 每个 的链接 地址 所以 我们能做的就是说 好了
we're gonna make a new variable called href and it's gonna be equal to link
我们要创建一个名为的新变量 href，它将 等于链接
because remember everything gives back this treated is linked and we'll put get
因为 记得一切都回馈 这个处理是相关的，我们将把get
href so again what this does is it says okay I know you're looking at this entire thing right here but we don't
href再说一遍它说的是什么 好吧， 我知道你在看这个 整个事情就在这里，但我们没有
want all this extra crap we don't like need the anchor tags and stuff like this
想要所有这些我们不喜欢的额外垃圾 需要锚标签和这样的东西
the only thing we want is the text that's inside this href attribute so for
我们 唯一 想要的是文字 这个href属性里面就是 这样的
each item what this is gonna do is it's gonna give you this and actually let me
这个项目将会是什么呢 要给你这个居然让我
print this out real quick and you guys are going to understand what I mean so
打印出来真的很快 ，你们 我 会 理解 我的意思
now if I print href let me run this real quick all right so of course if we just
现在，如果我打印href让我运行这个真实 快速没事所以当然，如果我们只是
run this right now nothing's going to happen because we didn't call it so
运行这个，现在什么也没有打算 因为我们没有这么称呼它
let's call it right there and just the test I'm going to throw in Mac's pages
让我们把它称为那里， 只是 测试我 要投入 Mac的页面
is one so now let me right click and run Bucky
是一个 所以现在让我右键单击并运行Bucky
and check it out and why is this not oh I see all right so what we did is we
并检查 出来，为什么这不是哦 我没事，所以我们做的就是我们
accidentally put the Paigey cattle 1 and we put this so since 1 is not less than
不小心 把Paigey牛 1和 我们把这个如此以来，1不小于
1 it never ran and also forgot to do one other thing we also need to increment the pages each time even though we're
1 它 从未 跑过，也忘了 做一个 我们还需要增加其他东西 每次都是这些页面，即使我们是
only searching one page right now so again let's run this and check it out so
只有一个搜索页面现在 这样 再次让我们运行它并检查出来
what this basically did is it went to that page and for every single um title
它基本上做了什么，它去 了 该页面和每个 单独的标题
link it pulled out the href or the URL and then it printed it out on the screen
链接它拉出了href或URL 然后将其打印在屏幕上
and then of course I went to the next page but that's when our condition broke
然后 我 当然 去了下一个 页面，但那是我们的条件破裂
right here so of course if we're actually crawling and gathering this
就在这里，当然，如果我们是 实际上爬行和收集这个
data it wouldn't be very helpful because this URL is great for you know whenever
数据不是很有用，因为 这个网址是伟大的，你 知道，每当
I was designing the website but if I try to go to one of these in my browser you
我正在设计网站，但如果我尝试 去其中的一个 在我的 浏览器 你
know it's not gonna it's not gonna happen so well is a better thing to do is if
知道它 不会不会 发生 这么好 是一个 更好的事情是，如果
you add actually let me just do the shortcut of this actually do throw it
你添加实际让我做的 这个的 捷径 实际上是扔它
away I guess so basically you have to look okay this URL ends it trade the
离开我想基本上你必须这样做 看起来没关系 这个URL结束了交易
trade directory so what we need to do is if we copy all of this right here
贸易目录所以我们需要做的是 如果我们在这里复制所有这些
we can build a complete URL by writing href put this equal to HTTPS Bucky's room dot org and then add the ending
我们可以通过写作来构建完整的URL HREF把这个等于 HTTPS 布凯 房间点组织 然后添加结尾
part of it and now whenever you run this we now have a full URL so again that URL
它的一部分， 现在每当你运行它 我们现在有一个完整的URL， 所以这个URL
works this one works this one works what we did is let me
这项工作有效 这个工作我们所做的就是让我
close these to the right we now successfully built a web crawler that goes through every single item and
把它们关在右边 我们现在成功构建了一个Web爬虫 即经过每一个 项目 和
pulls out the URL of it so again that is pretty much the very basics of how
再拉出它的URL就是这样 几乎是如何的基础知识
Google um pretty much pulls links from your website so another thing that I
谷歌几乎可以从中获取链接 你的 网站 是我的另一件事
want to do is I want to show you guys well what if you don't want the URL what
想要做的是我想告诉你们 那么如果您 不希望URL是什么呢？
if you just want the title or something well what you can do in that case is
如果你只想要标题 或其他东西 那么你在这种情况下可以做的是
this and even if you don't want the title this is actually a pretty good to
这个，即使你不想要 这 标题 实际上非常好
learn so for everything you pull out of a link it's good to store it in a new
了解 你所取出的 一切 一个链接，它很好地存储在一个新的
variable so set the title equal to this remember all of that linker information
变量因此将标题设置为等于此 记住所有链接器信息
is still in that link variable so you always add link now to get the
仍然在那个链接变量中，所以你 总是现在添加链接来获取
information inside it I just added edit this er equipment now the part inside
里面的 信息 我刚刚添加了编辑 这个设备现在是里面的部分
your link right here the string without any of the HTML that is actually a
您的链接在这里的 无 弦 任何居然 是 HTML的
parameter called string just gonna say okay this lick is the entire um HTML but
参数叫做字符串就好 说 好吧，这舔是整个 嗯HTML但是
we only want the text inside it so that's when you use string so now if we
我们只想要里面的文字 那就是当你使用字符串时，如果我们现在
were to do something like print title and run this what it's going to do is of
是做 印刷 标题的 事情 并运行它将要做的事情
course we printed the href as well but now we printed the title of it
当然我们也打印了href但是 现在我们打印出它的标题
underneath it so at this this is the URL for this item this is the URL for this item so on and so forth so check this
下面，它以这个 是 这样 的 URL 为这个 项目，这 是该网址 项目依此类推，所以检查一下
out we now have a beginning of a very simple but very cool web crawler spider
我们现在有一个非常的开始 简单但非常酷的网络爬虫蜘蛛
whatever you want to call it and in the next video what I'm going to show you
无论你想叫什么，还是在 下一个视频 我将向您展示的内容
guys how to do is actually make this more dynamic because right now we give a
伙计们 怎么做才是这个 更有活力， 因为现在我们给了一个
certain number of pages basically giving it a list of URLs and it can go to that
一定数量的页面基本上给予 它是一个URL列表， 它可以去那
and when it's done it's done but what if we wanted this web crawler to go on
当它完成它已经完成但是如果 我们希望这个网络抓取工具继续下去
forever such as we want to say okay go to a new page get those all let go
永远如我们 想说的好吧 到一个新的页面让那些都 放手
all of those links crawl those and on those pages gather those links crawl
所有这些链接都会抓取这些链接 那些页面收集这些链接爬行
those and it can just going keep going on and on forever well that's what I'm
那些它可以继续前进 上和 永远 嗯 ，这是我什么
gonna be showing you guys in the next tutorial but for now same guys for
要展示你在接下来的家伙 教程，但现在同样的家伙
watching don't forget subscribe and I will see them
看着不要 忘记订阅我 会看到他们